[{"answer": "He says you are very sad ridiculous man. I don't agree of course. And that you must pay someone to have sex like a prostitute. my friend is a prostitute. I'm sorry", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "He wants money", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I paid for those guitar cases", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "It was alright", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Yeah it was okay", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "The sets were good", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yeah. It was quite good actually. Some bits I really liked", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "The sets were excellent. Everything was big, you know, all the rubbish, coke cans, sweet wrappers, dustbins, so when you were watching it you felt cat size. It was really clever", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What's this", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "That's not a burn", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "In the world", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I do. I want to very badly", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "He left me my passport and ticket. It's pretty clear he wants to see me again", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No. But you tend to tie them up", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "And? What are you saying", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "And who says what is wrong", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "So what? Do you just switch off in your head or do you imagine you're with him, or what", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Sometimes which", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Sometimes", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Sometimes neither", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "So what did you want? I think we understand each other, no", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You don't understand you either", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You are pretty naive if you think it is", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I don't have nothing", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Nobody's that unhappy", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I don't want anyone to die", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I don't want anyone to die", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Except for Small Eyes", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "Birthday-Girl.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "What's your name", "qsentId": 30}]